[{"answer": " Hey, did you just wake up?  Its 4:30 in the afternoon", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 12, "question": "", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": "Yeah, I did.  I took a long nap.  I was so exhausted", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 13, "question": " Hey, did you just wake up?  Its 4:30 in the afternoon", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Why", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 14, "question": "Yeah, I did.  I took a long nap.  I was so exhausted", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Well, I had a test at 8:00 this morning, and I was up all night cramming for it", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Why", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Oh, no.  How do you think you did", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Well, I had a test at 8:00 this morning, and I was up all night cramming for it", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Not too well.  Ive got to stop waiting til the last minute to study", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Oh, no.  How do you think you did", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " It cant be good for you to keep pulling these all-nighters", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Not too well.  Ive got to stop waiting til the last minute to study", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " No, its not.  How do you do it", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 19, "question": " It cant be good for you to keep pulling these all-nighters", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " What do you mean", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 20, "question": " No, its not.  How do you do it", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " I mean I never see you cramming for a test or stressing out about school", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 21, "question": " What do you mean", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " Well, I guess I just have a different kind of study style than you", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 22, "question": " I mean I never see you cramming for a test or stressing out about school", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " But I need to change mine.  Can you give me some advice", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 26, "question": " Well, I guess I just have a different kind of study style than you", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " I mean, Im not an expert, but I guess I can tell you a few things", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 27, "question": " But I need to change mine.  Can you give me some advice", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " Sure, any advice will help", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 28, "question": " I mean, Im not an expert, but I guess I can tell you a few things", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " OK, instead of cramming all your studying into the night before a test, why  don", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 29, "question": " Sure, any advice will help", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " Is that what you do", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 33, "question": " OK, instead of cramming all your studying into the night before a test, why  don", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " Yeah.  I study for 30-40 minutes each day and its more manageable that way", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 34, "question": " Is that what you do", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " I guess I could do that.  It makes sense", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Yeah.  I study for 30-40 minutes each day and its more manageable that way", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " I found that joining a study group really helps me to keep up with studying", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 36, "question": " I guess I could do that.  It makes sense", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " Ive never been part of one of those before", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 37, "question": " I found that joining a study group really helps me to keep up with studying", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " Most classes have one.  You can join a group that meets to study once a week", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 38, "question": " Ive never been part of one of those before", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " I guess that would be helpful", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 43, "question": " Most classes have one.  You can join a group that meets to study once a week", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " Another thing I noticed is that if I see you studying, its out here in the living roo", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 44, "question": " I guess that would be helpful", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " So?  Thats where I study", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 48, "question": " Another thing I noticed is that if I see you studying, its out here in the living roo", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " I really dont think thats the best place.  Can you concentrate like that", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 49, "question": " So?  Thats where I study", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " Well, there are a lot of distractions", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 50, "question": " I really dont think thats the best place.  Can you concentrate like that", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " Thats what I would think.  You need a nice, comfortable, quiet place to stud", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 51, "question": " Well, there are a lot of distractions", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " Where do you study", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 55, "question": " Thats what I would think.  You need a nice, comfortable, quiet place to stud", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " I sit at the desk in my room with the door closed, or I go to the library", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 56, "question": " Where do you study", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " But I hate the library", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 57, "question": " I sit at the desk in my room with the door closed, or I go to the library", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " Its really quiet there and a great place to study", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 58, "question": " But I hate the library", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " Maybe I could go to a quiet coffee shop and sit and study", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 62, "question": " Its really quiet there and a great place to study", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " I think that could work.  Itd be better than in front of the TV", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 63, "question": " Maybe I could go to a quiet coffee shop and sit and study", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " OK.  Ill try", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 64, "question": " I think that could work.  Itd be better than in front of the TV", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Thats basically it.  I think just studying a little bit everyday in a quiet place  wil", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 65, "question": " OK.  Ill try", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " I hope so.  I need better grades next semester", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 69, "question": " Thats basically it.  I think just studying a little bit everyday in a quiet place  wil", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " You can get them if you try.  Hey, I was planning on going to the coffee sho", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 70, "question": " I hope so.  I need better grades next semester", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " Sure, Id love to", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 74, "question": " You can get them if you try.  Hey, I was planning on going to the coffee sho", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " OK.  Lets go around 6:00", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 75, "question": " Sure, Id love to", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " Itll be a great way for me to start my new, improved study habits", "docId": "05-08", "aSentId": 76, "question": " OK.  Lets go around 6:00", "qSentId": 75}]
